Everybody wanted to be in the Brat Pack. Except them.
BRATS is a documentary film directed by Andrew McCarthy.
In the 1980s, Andrew McCarthy was part of a young generation of actors who were set
to take over Hollywood after a string of successful teen movies.
However, when the New York magazine cover story in 1985 dubs them the Brat Pack, stars in the
making suddenly find themselves losing control over the trajectory of their careers.
Now, almost forty years later, McCarthy looks to reconnect with peers and co-stars
so that together they can reflect on their respective legacies.
Self, played by Andrew McCarthy.
Self, played by Emilio Estevez.
Self, played by Ally Sheedy.
Self, played by Demi Moore.
Self, played by Rob Lowe.
Self, played by Timothy Hutton.
Brats is a 2024 documentary film, directed by Andrew McCarthy.
It explores the Brat Pack, a group of young actors who frequently appeared together
in coming-of-age films, and the impact on their lives and careers.
It had its world premiere at the Tribeca Festival on June 7,
2024, and was released on June 13, 2024, by Hulu.
The film explores themes of teen movie, hollywood, 1980s.